buccaneers.com 2017-05-28

# Tampa Bay Buccaneers | Privacy

**Tampa Bay Buccaneers Website Privacy Policy**

**Posted: May 23, 2016**

This privacy policy applies to the Tampa Bay Buccaneers website located at www.buccaneers.com (the “Website”). The purpose of this privacy policy is to disclose to you what information we may collect, how we may collect it, with whom we may share it, and certain other matters related to such information, including the choices you have regarding our collection of information and our use and disclosure to other parties of information we may have collected from you.

The Website is operated by the Tampa Bay Buccaneers.

If you have questions or concerns regarding this statement, please contact [tbbadmin@buccaneers.nfl.com](mailto:tbbadmin@buccaneers.nfl.com?subject=Privacy%20Policy%20Feedback). If you have an unresolved privacy or data use concern that we have not addressed satisfactorily, please contact our U.S. based third party dispute resolution provider (free of charge) at <https://feedback-form.truste.com/watchdog/request>.

The Tampa Bay Buccaneers comply with the U.S. – E.U. Safe Harbor framework and the U.S. – Swiss Safe Harbor framework as set forth by the U.S.  Department of Commerce regarding the collection, use, and retention of personal data from European Union member countries and Switzerland.  The Tampa Bay Buccaneers adheres to the Safe Harbor Privacy Principles of notice, choice, onward transfer, security, data integrity, access, and enforcement.  To learn more about the Safe Harbor program, and to view The Tampa Bay Buccaneers certification, please visit http://export.gov/safeharbor.

When this privacy policy uses the term “personally identifiable information” or “personal information,” we mean information that identifies a particular individual, such as your full name, street address or email address. When other information, such as a favorite team or player, is associated with personal information, it also becomes personally identifiable information for the purposes of this privacy policy.

Please read the information below to learn more about our data collection policies and practices.

  1. Types Of Information That May Be Collected
  2. How Information May Be Collected
  3. How We Use The Information Collected
  4. With Whom The Information May Be Shared
  5. Security
  6. Chat Rooms, Forums, And Message Boards
  7. Links To Other Websites
  8. A Special Note For Parents Concerning Privacy
  9. Notification Of Changes And Your Acceptance Of The Privacy Policy
  10. Correcting/Updating Personal Information
  11. Your California Privacy Rights
  12. Questions About This Privacy Policy

**TYPES OF INFORMATION THAT MAY BE COLLECTED**

The following are the types of information we may collect:

Information You Provide Us: In the course of using the website, we may ask you to provide us with certain information, including contact information, such as your name, mailing address, email address or phone number, unique identifiers, such as your “message board user ID or user password, demographic information, such as your ticket holder status, financial information, such as your credit card number or similar information.

Site Usage Information: We may receive and store certain types of internet usage information whenever you visit the Website, such as your your IP address. See “IP Addresses and Click Stream Data” section below.

Email Communications: When you open emails from us, we may receive a confirmation noting you opened the email, if your computer supports such capabilities. We also may keep track of what emails we send you and what emails you may be receiving from our subsidiaries and affiliates. Additionally, we keep a record of what communications you have opted to receive or not to receive.

**HOW INFORMATION MAY BE COLLECTED**

We may collect information from you in several different areas on the Website, including but not limited to those described below:

Registration: You may be asked to complete a registration form and provide personally identifiable information; you may also be asked to choose a user ID and password in order to take advantage of certain features the Website may choose to offer, such as newsletters or contests. Participation in registration is voluntary and you will have the opportunity to decide whether or not to disclose information to the Website.

Newsletters and Website Emails: We offer free newsletters to share information with you about the Website, about us and our affiliates and subsidiaries, or about our marketing partners and advertisers and sponsors. You may receive a newsletter either by registering for a particular newsletter or in conjunction with a special feature or membership for which you have registered on the Website. Participation is voluntary and you will have the opportunity to decide whether or not to disclose information to the Website. You may also cancel your free email subscription by following the instructions provided on the Website or in the newsletter or email ([tbbadmin@buccaneers.nfl.com](mailto:tbbadmin@buccaneers.nfl.com?subject=Privacy%20Policy%20Feedback)).

Contests or Sweepstakes: We periodically operate contests and sweepstakes through the Website that may require registration or the submission of personal information. Participation is voluntary and you will have the opportunity to decide whether or not to disclose information to the Website. Your personally identifiable information may be used to contact you for winner notification, prize delivery confirmation or other related purposes, (see the rules of each contest for details about how your personal information will be used). We may also ask your permission to allow us to publicly post some of your information on the Website, such as on a winner’s page, in the event you win a contest or sweepstakes. Except as required by applicable law, we will not post your information without your permission. All contests on the Website are run in-house and do not provide information to third parties.

Surveys or Voting: From time-to-time we may request personally identifiable information from you in conjunction with a survey or voting poll. Participation is voluntary and you will have the opportunity to decide whether or not to disclose information to the Website.

Games: When you register to play games on our Website, you may be asked to provide personally identifiable information.

Tracking Technologies: The use of cookies by or similar tracking technologies by us or our third party partners or affiliates is used to identify your browser to the Website whenever your computer is used to visit the Website. Technologies also let us know how many people visit our Website and where visitors go on the site.  In addition, technologies can let us know non-personally identifiable information, like what web browser is being used to access the website.  For registered users, technologies can make using the Website easier for you by saving information such as your passwords or preferences. By tracking how and when you use the Website, technologies help us determine which areas are popular and which are not. Many improvements and updates to the Websites are based on data obtained from technologies.  Accepting these technologies allows you, among other things to personalize your experience. 

We partner with a third party to either display advertising on our website or to manage our advertising on other sites.  Our third party partner may use technologies such as cookies to gather information about your activities on this website and other sites in order to provide you advertising based upon your browsing activities and interests.  If you wish to not have this information used for the purpose of serving you interest-based ads, you may opt-out by clicking [here](http://preferences-mgr.truste.com/) (or if located in the European Union click [here](http://youronlinechoices.eu/)).  Please note this does not opt you out of being served ads.  You will continue to receive generic ads.

IP Addresses and Click-Stream Data: We may collect IP addresses and/or click-stream data. An IP address is a number associated with the service through which you access the Internet, like your ISP (Internet service provider), your company, or your university. Standing alone, your IP address is not personally identifiable. At times, we also use IP addresses for purposes of system administration and to report aggregate information to our advertisers and sponsors, for example regarding the frequency with which our guests visit various parts of our sites. We may combine this information with personally identifiable information. Click-stream data is information collected by our computers when you request Web pages from the Website. Click-stream data may include such information as the page served, the time, the source of the request, the type of browser making the request, the preceding page view and other such non-personal information. When analyzed, this data helps us analyze how visitors arrive at the Website, what type of content is most popular, what type of visitors in the aggregate are interested in particular kinds of content and advertising, and the like.

Transaction Information: If you conduct a financial transaction with our Website, such as the payment of season ticket invoices or the purchase of products, we will ask you to complete an order form that will request certain information from you, including contact information, demographic information and financial information. We will use this information to complete the transaction that you have requested, i.e., to deliver the information, products or other services that you order, and to invoice you. For your protection, such information is collected and stored through encrypted means.

**HOW WE USE THE INFORMATION COLLECTED**

As applicable, the information you provide to us may be used to:

contact you about the Website;

contact you relating to your membership status;

confirm or fulfill an order you have made;

inform you of a prize you have won;

monitor or improve the use of the Website;

customize the advertising and content you see;

monitor compliance with our terms and conditions of use of the Website; and

send you promotional material or special offers on behalf of our marketing partners and/or their respective affiliates and subsidiaries and other third parties.

**WITH WHOM THE INFORMATION MAY BE SHARED**

At times, we may share your personal information with others for various purposes. The following outlines the ways in which your information may be shared with others and the ways in which you may opt-out of having your information shared:

Agents: We employ other businesses, certain services and individuals to perform functions on our behalf. Examples include fulfilling orders, sending e-mail, removing repetitive information from customer lists, processing credit card payments, and providing customer service. They may have access to personally identifiable information needed to perform their functions, but may not use it for their own purposes, like sending you marketing offers about their products.

Aggregate Information: We may share aggregate information, such as demographics and Website usage statistics, with advertisers, sponsors or other organizations. When this type of information is shared, the other parties do not have access to your personally identifiable information.

Other Promotional Offers: We may send offers to you on behalf of our marketing partners. When we do this, we do not give that partner your name and address. If you do not want to receive such offers, you may use the opt out method detailed in the email.

Business Transfers: In the event that all or substantially all of our assets are sold or transferred to another party, or another transaction occurs in which your personally identifiable information is one of the business assets transferred, all personally identifiable information that has been collected and saved may be one of the business assets we transfer. See “Your Acceptance of the privacy policy and notification of changes to the policy” section below.

Administrative or Legal Process: Your personal information may be transferred to third parties without notice to you in order to comply with applicable law, law enforcement agencies, to protect our rights, or protect the rights of other users of this website.

We do not share, sell, rent or trade your personal information with third parties for their promotional purposes.

**PUBLIC FORUMS**

Our websites offers publicly accessible blogs or community forums.  You should be aware that any information you provide in these areas may be read, collected, and used by others who access them. To request removal of your personal information from public areas of the site, please contact us at the email address listed below.  In some cases, we may not be able to remove your personal information, in which case we will let you know if we are unable to do so and why.

**LINKS TO OTHER WEBSITES**

You should be aware that when you are on the Website you could be directed to other Websites beyond our control. For example, if you "click" on a banner advertisement, the "click" may take you off the Website onto a different Website. This includes links from advertisers, sponsors and marketing partners that may use the Website's logo as part of a co-branding agreement. These other Websites may send their own cookies to you, independently collect data or solicit personal information and may or may not have their own published privacy policies. If you visit a Website that is linked to our Website, you should consult that Website's privacy policy before providing any personal information.

**SECURITY**

The security of your personal information is important to us.  We follow generally accepted standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once it is received.  If you have any questions about the security of your personal information, you may contact us at the email address listed below.

**A SPECIAL NOTE FOR PARENTS CONCERNING PRIVACY**

The Website is a general audience Website. We do not currently collect any personal information from children under the age of thirteen on the Website. If in the future, we collect personally identifiable information from children, it will do so in compliance with the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act of 1998 (15 U.S.C. 6501 et seq.) including, without limitation, obtaining necessary parental consent.

The Internet offers children wonderful educational and entertainment resources. Your guidance and involvement are essential to help ensure that children have a safe and rewarding online experience. We encourage you to visit the Direct Marketing Association's Web Website (www.the-dma.org) and explore the Get CyberSavvy! Program as well as the GetNetWise Website (www.getnetwise.org) to learn more about parental control tools.

**YOUR ACCEPTANCE OF THE PRIVACY POLICY AND NOTIFICATION OF CHANGES TO THE POLICY**

By using this Website, you signify your agreement to the terms of our privacy policy. We may amend this privacy policy at any time. If we make a material change to the way in which we collect, use, and/or share your personal information, we will post a notice on our website and / or send an email to users who have provided an email address. We will assume that you have given your permission for your information to be used under the terms of the new privacy policy, if you do not respond to our email within thirty days or continue to use the Website thirty days after a notice is posted. Please note that you should always update your personal information to provide us with a current email address.

Please note that the Services are directed towards users who reside in the United States. By using the Services, you consent to the collection, storage, processing, and transfer of your information in and to the United States, or other countries and territories, pursuant to the laws of the United States. While some of these countries may not offer the same level of privacy protection as your own, we commit to uphold the privacy protections as explained in this Policy.

**CORRECTING/UPDATING PERSONAL INFORMATION**

If your personally identifiable information changes (such as your email address or zip code), or if you no longer desire to access our Website, we will endeavor to provide a way to correct, update, delete, or remove the personal data you have provided to us. This can be done by using an opt out message in an email, or by emailing us at [tbbadmin@buccaneers.nfl.com](mailto:tbbadmin@buccaneers.nfl.com).  We will respond to your request within a reasonable timeframe.

**YOUR CALIFORNIA PRIVACY RIGHTS**

A California privacy law that went into effect on January 1, 2005, allows California residents to obtain specific information about a business’s privacy practices if it shares information with other companies for those companies’ direct marketing purposes.

As explained in this privacy policy, whenever you agree to let us collect personal information about you, we will always provide you with an option to prevent this information from being shared for non-administrative purposes with third parties. You can exercise this option at any time by following the steps outlined above.

Because this website has a comprehensive privacy policy and provides you with details on how you may opt-in / opt-out of the use of your personal information by third parties for direct marketing purposes, we are not required to provide you with this information.

If you are a California resident and have questions about our compliance with this law, please send an email to [tbbadmin@buccaneers.nfl.com](mailto:tbbadmin@buccaneers.nfl.com?subject=Privacy%20Policy%20Feedback) or write to us at CA Privacy Rights, Tampa Bay Buccaneers, One Buccaneer Place, Tampa, FL 33624.

**QUESTIONS ABOUT THIS PRIVACY POLICY**

If you have any questions about this privacy policy or the privacy practices of this Website, contact [tbbadmin@buccaneers.nfl.com](mailto:tbbadmin@buccaneers.nfl.com?subject=Privacy%20Policy%20Feedback).

Questions regarding this statement should be directed to:

Attn: Website Privacy Policy

Tampa Bay Buccaneers, One Buccaneer Place, Tampa, FL 33624.
